Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - P
        - Priest, Maxi - Just a little bit longer, 1990; SR-28185; Priest, Maxi (Box 394)
          Catalog # DMD 1586; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-59650-59651-2
          Charisma
        - Priest, Maxi - The Maxi Priest E.P. (Disc one), 1991; SR-28186; Priest, Maxi (Box 394)
          In same jacket as # SR-28187. Double album.
          Catalog # TENDJ 343; A-side Matrix # TENDJ 343 A 1U - 1 - 1
          10 Records
        - Priest, Maxi - The Maxi Priest E.P. (Disc two), 1991; SR-28187; Priest, Maxi (Box 394)
          In same jacket as # SR-28186. Double album.
          Catalog # TENDJ 343; A-side Matrix # TENDJ 343 C 1U - 1 - 1
        - Priest, Maxi - Some guys have all the luck, 1987; SR-28188; Priest, Maxi (Box 394)
          Catalog # TENT 198; A-side Matrix # TENT 198 A-1U-1-2-1 TOWNHOUSE DMM
        - Prime Time - So damn tuff; He's deff, 1987; SR-28189; Prime Time (Box 394)
          Catalog # ST PT 712; A-side Matrix # 712-A O-D2-2
          Hits in the Groove
        - Primeridian - Zero degrees longitude, 1999; SR-28190; Primeridian (Box 394)
          Catalog # GDR 071; A-side Matrix # GDR-071 A
          Guidance Recordings
        - Primeridian - Ring around the lyrical, 2000; SR-28191; Primeridian (Box 394)
          Catalog # GDR 080; A-side Matrix # GDR-080 A
        - Prince - Gold, 1995; SR-13104; Prince; Artist; New Power Generation (Box 394)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7941; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-7941-A
        - Prince - 7, 1992; SR-28193; Prince; New Power Generation (Box 394)
          Catalog # 0-40574; A-side Matrix # 0-40574-A SR1
        - Prince - Delirious, 1982; SR-28194; Prince (Box 395)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2080; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2080-SH1 B-18581-SH1 SLM 5307 1-1
        - Prince - Sign "o" the times, 1987; SR-28195; Prince (Box 395)
          Catalog # 0-20648; A-side Matrix # 0-20648-A-SR2
          Paisley Park
        - Prince - Let's pretend we're married, 1983; SR-28196; Prince (Box 395)
          Catalog # 0-20170; A-side Matrix # 0-20170-A-SR1 1-2
        - Prince - 1999, 1982; SR-28197; Prince (Box 395)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2042; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2042-SH1 B-18168-SH1 SLM 4539
        - Prince - The most beautiful girl in the world, 1994; SR-28198; Prince; Artist (Box 395)
          Catalog # BR-72514-1; A-side Matrix # BR-72514-1
          Bellmark Records
        - Prince - The greatest romance ever sold, 1999; SR-28199; Prince; Artist (Box 395)
          Catalog # ARDP-3764; A-side Matrix # TD ARDP-3764-SA
        - Prince - Money don't matter 2 night, 1992; SR-28200; Prince; New Power Generation (Box 395)
          Catalog # PRO-A-5298; A-side Matrix # Precision T.D. PRO-A1-5298-SR1-DMM SP1-1
        - Prince - I would die 4 u (extended version), 1984; SR-28201; Prince; Revolution (Box 395)
          Catalog # 0-20291; A-side Matrix # 0-20291-A-S-SR2
        - Prince - If I was your girlfriend, 1987; SR-28202; Prince (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28203. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 0-20697; A-side Matrix # 0-20697-A-SR1
        - Prince - If I was your girlfriend, 1987; SR-28203; Prince (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28202. 2 copies.
        - Prince - Little red corvette, 1982; SR-28204; Prince (Box 395)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2001; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2001-SH1 B-17708 SLM 3617 1-1
        - Prince - I hate u, 1995; SR-28205; Prince; Artist (Box 395)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7594; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-7594-A-SR1
        - Prince - I wish u heaven, 1988; SR-28206; Prince (Box 395)
          Catalog # 0-21074; A-side Matrix # 0-21074-A-SH2 Townhouse B-33063-SH2 22632 1-1
        - Prince - Rave un2 the joy fantastic (Disc one), 1999; SR-28207; Prince; Artist (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28208. Double album.
          Catalog # 07822-14624-1; A-side Matrix # 07822-14624-1-SA
        - Prince - Rave un2 the joy fantastic (Disc two), 1999; SR-28208; Prince; Artist (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28207. Double album.
          Catalog # 07822-14624-1; A-side Matrix # 07822-14624-1-SC
        - Prince - Alphabet st., 1988; SR-28209; Prince (Box 395)
          Catalog # 0-20930; A-side Matrix # 0-20930-A-SH1 B-30977-SH 20310 1-2
        - Prince - Sign "o" the times, 1987; SR-28210; Prince (Box 395)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2687; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2687-SH1 B-26704-SH1 15722 1-1
        - Prince - Kiss, 1986; SR-28211; Prince; Revolution (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28212. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 0-20442; A-side Matrix # 0-20442-A-SR2
        - Prince - Kiss, 1986; SR-28212; Prince; Revolution (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28211. 2 copies.
        - Prince - I could never take the place of your man, 1987; SR-28213; Prince (Box 395)
          Different jacket
          Catalog # W8288TP; A-side Matrix # W8288TP A SW PJ
        - Prince - Sexy mf, 1992; SR-28214; Prince; New Power Generation (Box 395)
          Catalog # W0123 T; A-side Matrix # WMME Alsdorf 936 240481-0-A
        - Prince - The remixes (Disc one), 2004; SR-28215; Prince (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28216. Double album.
          Catalog # PNC 001; A-side Matrix # PNC 001 A
          PNC Records
        - Prince - The remixes (Disc two), 2004; SR-28216; Prince (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28215. Double album.
          Catalog # PNC 001; A-side Matrix # PNC 001 C
        - Prince - America, 1985; SR-28217; Prince; Revolution (Box 395)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2300; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-2300 SH-1 B-21921-SH1 SLM 10686 1-1
        - Prince - Rave un2 the joy fantastic, 1999; SR-28218; Prince; Artist (Box 395)
        - Prince - Letitgo, 1994; SR-28219; Prince (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28220. Different discs.
          Catalog # PRO-A-7000; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-7000-SR1
        - Prince - Letitgo, 1994; SR-28220; Prince (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28219. Different discs.
          Catalog # 0-41745-A; A-side Matrix # 0-41745-A-SR1
        - Prince - I wish u heaven, 1988; SR-28221; Prince (Box 395)
        - Prince - Face down, 1997; SR-28222; Prince; Artist (Box 395)
          Catalog # SPRO 11698; A-side Matrix # SPRO-11698-A-1
          NPG Records
        - Prince - Let's pretend we're married, 1983; SR-28223; Prince (Box 395)
          Catalog # 0-20170; A-side Matrix # 0-20170-A-SR1
        - Prince - Glam slam, 1988; SR-28224; Prince (Box 395)
          Catalog # 0-21005; A-side Matrix # 21380 SPI-2 0- B-31921-SRI-DMM 0 21005 A DMM SRI SP-AR STERLING TJ --2
        - Prince - I would die 4 u (extended version), 1984; SR-28225; Prince; Revolution (Box 395)
          Catalog # 0-20291; A-side Matrix # 0-20291-A-S-SR1
        - Prince - Pop life (Disc one), 1986; SR-28226; Prince; Revolution (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28227. Double album.
          Catalog # 1861121; A-side Matrix # LANE STING 1999-A
          Northlake Records
        - Prince - Pop life (Disc two), 1986; SR-28227; Prince; Revolution (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28226. Double album.
          Catalog # 1861121; A-side Matrix # LANE STING 1999-C
        - Prince - If I was your girlfriend, 1987; SR-28228; Prince (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28229. Different discs.
          Catalog # PRO-A-2758; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2758-SH1 B-27706-SH1 16777 1-1
        - Prince - If I was your girlfriend, 1987; SR-28229; Prince (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28228. Different discs.
          Catalog # 0-20697; A-side Matrix # 0-20697-A-SH1 B-27371-SH 16414 1-1
        - Prince - The rainbow children (Disc one), 2001; SR-28230; Prince (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28231. Double album.
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # 0110x29A
          Redline Entertainment
          Minneapolis, Minnesota
        - Prince - The rainbow children (Disc two), 2001; SR-28231; Prince (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28230. Double album.
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # 0110x30C
        - Prince - When doves cry, 1984; SR-28232; Prince (Box 395)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2139; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2139-REI-SH1 B-19244-Rei-SH1 SLM 6519 1-1
        - Prince - 1999, 1982; SR-28233; Prince (Box 395)
          Catalog # PRO-A-1070; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-1070-SH1 B-17178-SH1 2565 + SLM
        - Prince - The future, 1989; SR-28234; Prince (Box 395)
          Catalog # 7599-21570-0; A-side Matrix # R/S Alsdorf 759 921570-0-A
        - Prince - Thieves in the temple (12" remixes), 1990; SR-28235; Prince (Box 395)
          Catalog # 0-21598; A-side Matrix # MASTERDISK 0-21598-A-SR1 1-1
        - Prince - New power generation, 1990; SR-28236; Prince (Box 395)
          Catalog # 0-21783; A-side Matrix # 0-21783-A-REI-SR1-DMM
        - Prince - The gold experience (Disc one), 1995; SR-28237; Prince; Artist (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28238. Double album.ripped jacket
          Catalog # PRO-A-7835; A-side Matrix # "DEFEND YOUR RIGHT 2 DIE AND LIVE AGAIN" PRO-A-7835-A-SR-1
        - Prince - The gold experience (Disc two), 1995; SR-28238; Prince; Artist (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28237. Double album.ripped jacket
          Catalog # PRO-A-7835; A-side Matrix # "THERE'S A MOUNTAIN AND IT'S MIGHTY HIGH. U CANNOT SEE THE TOP UNLESS U FLY" PRO-A-7835-C-SR-1
        - Prince - Japan (Disc one), 1989; SR-28239; Prince (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28240. Double album.
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # BP 1
          Todeskuss
        - Prince - Japan (Disc two), 1989; SR-28240; Prince (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28239. Double album.
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # PB 3
        - Prince - Anotherloverholenyohead, 1986; SR-28241; Prince; Revolution (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28242. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 0-20516; A-side Matrix # 0-20516-A SH2 B-24739-SH2 13651 1-1
        - Prince - Anotherloverholenyohead, 1986; SR-28242; Prince; Revolution (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28241. 2 copies.
        - Prince - Somebody's somebody (remix), 1997; SR-28243; Prince; Artist (Box 395)
          Catalog # SPRO-11672; A-side Matrix # SPRO-11672-1-A-REI
        - Prince - America, 1985; SR-28244; Prince; Revolution (Box 395)
          Catalog # 0-20389; A-side Matrix # 0-20389-A SH-1 B-21968-SH1 SLM 10764 1-1
        - Prince - My name is Prince (remixes), 1992; SR-28245; Prince; New Power Generation (Box 395)
          Catalog # 9362-40708-0; A-side Matrix # WMME Alsdorf 936 240708-0-A
        - Prince - Money don't matter 2 night, 1992; SR-28246; Prince; New Power Generation (Box 395)
          Catalog # 9362-40421-0; A-side Matrix # ORLAKE W-0091+TP-1
        - Prince - Black album, 1994; SR-28247; Prince (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28248. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PRO-A-7330; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-7330-SR2
        - Prince - Black album, 1994; SR-28248; Prince (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28247. 2 copies.
        - Prince - Purple medley, 1995; SR-28249; Prince (Box 395)
          Catalog # 0-43503; A-side Matrix # 0-43503-A SR-1 1-1
        - Prince - I could never take the place of your man, 1987; SR-28250; Prince (Box 395)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2770; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2770-SH1 B-29507-SH1 18669 1-1
        - Prince - Pink cashmere, 1993; SR-28251; Prince (Box 395)
          Catalog # PRO-A-5993; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-5993-SR2 DMM RB PRECISION SD 1-1
        - Prince - Little red corvette, 1982; SR-28252; Prince (Box 395)
        - Prince - Uptown, 1980; SR-28253; Prince (Box 395)
          Catalog # PRO-A-904; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-904-A1 B-15277
        - Prince - Purple medley, 1995; SR-28254; Prince (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28255. 2 copies.different jacket
          Catalog # PRO-A-7481; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-7481 A REI SR1 1-1
        - Prince - Purple medley, 1995; SR-28255; Prince (Box 395)
          In same jacket as # SR-28254. 2 copies.different jacket
        - Prince - 1999 (Disc one), 1982; SR-28256; Prince (Box 395)
          Catalog # 1-23720; A-side Matrix # 1-23720-A-SR4 SP 1-2
        - Prince - Let's pretend we're married; D.M.S.R.; Automatic, 1982; SR-28257; Prince (Box 395)
          Catalog # PRO-A-1082; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-1082-SH1 B-17438-SH1 3127 + SLM
        - Prince - I could never take the place of your man, 1987; SR-28258; Prince (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28259. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 0-20728; A-side Matrix # AL-SP 0-20728-A-SH2 B-29464-SH2 18618 SP0-1
        - Prince - I could never take the place of your man, 1987; SR-28259; Prince (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28258. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 0-20728; A-side Matrix # AL-SP 0-20728-A-SH2 B-29464-SH2 18618 0-1
        - Prince - Controversy, 1981; SR-28260; Prince (Box 396)
          Catalog # BSK 3601; A-side Matrix # 0-1 SM3-1 BSK-1-3601-(RE-1)-S2 + SP SLM + 952
        - Prince - If I was your girlfriend, 1987; SR-28261; Prince (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28262. 2 copies.
        - Prince - If I was your girlfriend, 1987; SR-28262; Prince (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28261. 2 copies.
        - Prince - Kiss; Pop life; 1999; I wanna be your lover; If I was your girlfriend, 2005; SR-28263; Prince (Box 396)
          Catalog # HP-006; A-side Matrix # HP-6-A
          House Party
        - Prince - Girls & boys, 1986; SR-28264; Prince; Revolution (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28265. Different discs.
          Catalog # 920 532-0; A-side Matrix # R/S Alsdorf 920532-0-Axx BE
        - Prince - Let's go crazy; Take me with u; Erotic city, 1985; SR-28265; Prince; Revolution (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28264. Different discs.
          Catalog # 920 317-0; A-side Matrix # R/S Alsdorf 920317-0-A
        - Prince - Raspberry beret, 1985; SR-28266; Prince; Revolution (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28267. Different discs.
          Catalog # 0-20355; A-side Matrix # 0-20355-A-SH1 B-21453-SH1 SLM 9941 1-1
        - Prince - Paisley Park, 1985; SR-28267; Prince; Revolution (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28266. Different discs.
          Catalog # W9052; A-side Matrix # W9052T A//1 420V
        - Prince - Sign "o" the times (Disc one), 1987; SR-28268; Prince (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28269. Double album.
          Catalog # 1-25577; A-side Matrix # 1-25577-A-SH4 B-26794-SH4 15824 1-1
        - Prince - Sign "o" the times (Disc two), 1987; SR-28269; Prince (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28268. Double album.
          Catalog # 1-25577; A-side Matrix # 1-25577-C-SH1 B-26796-SH1 15825 1-3
        - Prince - 1999, 1998; SR-28270; Prince; Sanchez, Roger (Box 396)
          Catalog # 1999010; A-side Matrix # 1999010 A-1-1-1
        - Prince - The greatest romance ever sold, 1999; SR-28271; Prince; Artist (Box 396)
        - Prince - Around the world in a day, 1985; SR-28272; Prince; Revolution (Box 396)
          Catalog # 1-25286; A-side Matrix # 1-25286A-SR7 1-4
        - Prince - Controversy, 1981; SR-28273; Prince (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28274. 2 copies.
          Catalog # BSK 3601; A-side Matrix # B-16192-REI-S2 BSK-1-3601-(RE-1)-S2 + SLM +++ 952
        - Prince - Controversy, 1981; SR-28274; Prince (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28273. 2 copies.
        - Prince - Delirious, 1982; SR-28275; Prince (Box 396)
        - Prince - Kiss, 1986; SR-28276; Prince; Revolution (Box 396)
          Catalog # 0-20442; A-side Matrix # 0-20442-A-SR1 1-1
        - Prince - BatmanTM motion picture soundtrack, 1989; SR-28277; Prince (Box 396)
          Catalog # 1-25936; A-side Matrix # 1-25936-A SR1-DMM SP1-2 MASTERDISK DMM -HW
        - Prince - World tour 1987 (Disc one), 1987; SR-28278; Prince (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28279. Double album.
          Catalog # 25510/1; A-side Matrix # 25510/1PRI-A
        - Prince - World tour 1987 (Disc two), 1987; SR-28279; Prince (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28278. Double album.
          Catalog # 25510/1; A-side Matrix # 25510/1PRI/C
        - Prince - Try out records, 1987; SR-28280; Prince (Box 396)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # ROV 01-A
          Aaron Records
        - Prince - U got the look, 1987; SR-28281; Prince (Box 396)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2771; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-2771-SH1 B-28063-SH1 17126 1-2
        - Prince - Let's work, 1982; SR-28282; Prince (Box 396)
          Catalog # PRO-A-1004; A-side Matrix # B-16464-A1 PRO-A-1004-ZCA-1256-V2-S-A1
        - Prince - Sign "o" the times, 1987; SR-28283; Prince (Box 396)
          Catalog # W 8399; A-side Matrix # W8399T-A DAMONT
        - Prince - Cream, 1991; SR-28284; Prince; New Power Generation (Box 396)
          Catalog # 9362-40213-0; A-side Matrix # WMME Alsdorf 936 240213-0-A
        - Prince - Letitgo, 1994; SR-28285; Prince (Box 396)
          Catalog # 0-41745; A-side Matrix # 0-41745-A-SR1
        - Prince - The beautiful experience, 1994; SR-28286; Prince; Artist (Box 396)
          Catalog # SPRO 72516; A-side Matrix # BR-72516-1-A
        - Prince - Pop life, 1985; SR-28287; Prince; Revolution (Box 396)
          Catalog # 0-20357; A-side Matrix # 0-20357-4-REI-SR1 1-1
        - Prince - Pop life, 1985; SR-28288; Prince; Revolution (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28289. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 0-20357; A-side Matrix # 0-20357-A-REI-SH1 B-21451-REI-SH1 SLM 9940 1-3
        - Prince - Pop life, 1985; SR-28289; Prince; Revolution (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28288. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 0-20357; A-side Matrix # 0-20357-A-REI-SR1 1-1SMI1
        - Prince - Graffiti bridge (Disc one), 1990; SR-28290; Prince (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28291. Double album.
          Catalog # 1-27493; A-side Matrix # 1-27493-A-SR3-DMM SP1-3 Masterdisk
        - Prince - Graffiti bridge (Disc two), 1990; SR-28291; Prince (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28290. Double album.
          Catalog # 1-27493; A-side Matrix # 1-27493-C-SR1-DMM SP1-1 MASTERDISK
        - Prince - Black album, 1987; SR-28292; Prince (Box 396)
          Catalog # 925 677-1; A-side Matrix # R/S ALSDORF 925677-1-A2
        - Prince B - Ode to a forgetful mind (it's a shame), 1989; SR-28293; Prince B (Box 396)
          Catalog # WAR-057; A-side Matrix # "ODE TO A WASTE OF VINYL" WAR 057A 1-1 F/W
          Pet Project
        - Prince Buster - Fabulous greatest hits, 1968; SR-28294; Prince Buster (Box 396)
          ripped jacket
          Catalog # MS.1; A-side Matrix # MS+1 A
          Fab
        - Prince Charles - Cash (cash money) (extended version), 1983; SR-28295; Prince Charles; City Beat Band (Box 396)
          Catalog # VR 596-12; A-side Matrix # TOWNHOUSE VS-596-12-A2
        - Prince Charles - More money, 1984; SR-28296; Prince Charles; City Beat Band (Box 396)
          Catalog # VS 669-12; A-side Matrix # VS 66912 A-1U-1-1-x1
        - Prince Charles - Gang wars, 1980; SR-28297; Prince Charles; City Beat Band (Box 396)
          Catalog # HCM 62680; A-side Matrix # HMC-62680-A SPR-62650-A (OTL-8005)
          Solid Platinum Records
          Boston, Massachusetts
        - Prince Dominique - The outlaw, 1994; SR-28298; Prince Dominique (Box 396)
          Catalog # 70007-1; A-side Matrix # 70007-1 A S-29908
          Radical Records
        - Prince Dominique - The outlaw, 1994; SR-28299; Prince Dominique (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28300. 2 copies.
        - Prince Dominique - The outlaw, 1994; SR-28300; Prince Dominique (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28299. 2 copies.
        - Prince Markie Dee - Crunchtime, 1995; SR-28301; Prince Markie Dee (Box 396)
          Catalog # 374631326-1; A-side Matrix # MASTERDISK TD 37463-1336-1-A-SP1
        - Prince of Darkness - Life; Mortal combat, 1996; SR-28302; Prince of Darkness (Box 396)
          Catalog # 12-PO 371; A-side Matrix # PA 496 12-PO-371
          B.U.M. Records
          Waycross, Georgia
        - Prince Paul - Handle your time, 1999; SR-28303; Prince Paul; XZIBIT; Sadat X (Box 396)
          Catalog # TB 343; A-side Matrix # TB-343-A
        - Prince Paul - Handle your time, 1999; SR-28304; Prince Paul; XZIBIT; Sadat X (Box 396)
        - Prince Paul - Handle your time, 1999; SR-28305; Prince Paul; XZIBIT; Sadat X (Box 396)
        - Prince Paul - More than u know, 1998; SR-28306; Prince Paul; De La Soul (Box 396)
          Catalog # TB 334; A-side Matrix # TB-334-A
        - Prince Paul - More than u know, 1998; SR-28307; Prince Paul; De La Soul (Box 396)
        - Prince Paul - Psychoanalysis (what is it?), 1996; SR-28308; Prince Paul (Box 396)
          Catalog # 01210-1; A-side Matrix # EFA-LP-01210 A DMM GP
          EFA
        - Prince Paul - A prince among thieves (Disc two), 1999; SR-28309; Prince Paul (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28310. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TB 1210; A-side Matrix # TB-1210-C-REI CUT BY "THE INHABITANT"
        - Prince Paul - A prince among thieves (Disc two), 1999; SR-28310; Prince Paul (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28309. 2 copies.
        - Prince Paul - A prince among thieves (Disc one), 1999; SR-28311; Prince Paul (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28312. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TB 1210; A-side Matrix # TB-1210-A
        - Prince Paul - A prince among thieves (Disc one), 1999; SR-28312; Prince Paul (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28311. 2 copies.
        - Prince Paul - Psychoanalysis (what is it?) (Disc one), 1997; SR-25091; Prince Paul (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-25092; SR-25093. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TB 1209; A-side Matrix # TB 1209-A
        - Prince Paul - Psychoanalysis (what is it?) (Disc one), 1997; SR-25092; Prince Paul (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-25091; SR-25093. Double album.
        - Prince Paul - Psychoanalysis (what is it?) (Disc two), 1997; SR-25093; Prince Paul (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-25091; SR-25092. Double album.
        - Prince Paul - Psychoanalysis (what is it?) (Disc two), 1997; SR-25094; Prince Paul (Box 396)
        - Prince Po - Run wit it, 2002; SR-28313; Prince Po (Box 396)
          Catalog # FB200026; A-side Matrix # FB-200026-SA MASTERDISK
          Fully-Blown Recordings
        - Prince Rahiem - Rock wit' it, 1994; SR-28314; Prince Rahiem (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28315. Different discs.
          Catalog # 162-440 597-1; A-side Matrix # 162-440-597-1-AS MASTERDISK HVBTV
        - Prince Rahiem - Rock wit' it, 1994; SR-28315; Prince Rahiem (Box 396)
          In same jacket as # SR-28314. Different discs.
          Catalog # 162-440 597-1DJ; A-side Matrix # 162-440-597-1-AS MASTERDISK HVBTV
        - Prince Whipper Whip - Back 4 more whipnotizing, 1988; SR-28316; Prince Whipper Whip (Box 397)
          In same jacket as # SR-28317. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SW-6396; A-side Matrix # SW-6396-1A G-1 B-30550-G1 19857 1-1 DISS
          Cold Diss Records
        - Prince Whipper Whip - Back 4 more whipnotizing, 1988; SR-28317; Prince Whipper Whip (Box 397)
          In same jacket as # SR-28316. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SW-6396; A-side Matrix # SW-6396-1A G-1 B-30551-G1 19858 1-1
        - Prince Whipper Whip - Back 4 more whipnotizing, 1988; SR-28318; Prince Whipper Whip (Box 397)
        - Princess - Say I'm your number one, 1985; SR-28319; Princess (Box 397)
          Catalog # NP 50035; A-side Matrix # NP-50035-A
        - Principle, Jamie - Date with the rain, 1990; SR-28320; Principle, Jamie (Box 397)
          Catalog # DMD 1464; A-side Matrix # ATLANTIC STUDIOS D.K. ST-DM-58232-1